Adress: 46 Olivia Street

Liverpool L20 2ES

Email Adress: dianacozuc@yahoo.com

Telephone number: 0748 105 3280

Country of born:Romania

Country of living: UK

Diana Cozuc

Personal Profile

I am a very positive, confident and conscientious person, capable of working as a motivated team member or independently adopting a practical approach using own initiative. Trustworthy, hardworking and reliable with excellent communication and IT skills and the ability to adapt to new situations. Sociable personality with a friendly approach. By the time,i have experienced three areas of work: Fashion model, Comercial activities and Transport manager.

Work History

Fashion model Country: Romania

2012-2015

A Fashion Model with experience in industrial projects, successfully modeled for brands such as :L'oreal Paris , Atmosphere, Airsoft.

• Known for being flexible, adaptable, very stylish, versatile, efficient, hard-working, good at taking directions and capable of wearing all types of clothing styles.

Shop Assistant Country: UK -International Food Store Boston 03-08.2015

Duties:

- •Operating the tills, including cashing up and completing paper work at the start and end of shift.
- •Assisting customers in the selection and purchase of items.
- •Completing sales sheets at the end of the day.
- •Ensuring that the shop counter is always manned.
- •Processing cash and credit card transactions accurately & efficiently.
- •Managing the till, taking money from customers and hanging out receipts.
- •When required wrapping up purchased items for customers.
- •Following policies & procedures relating to cash & stock handling.
- •Checking the inventory listing with actual stock on the shop shelves and reporting and discrepancies to managers.

- •Keeping merchandise orderly and neat in appearance.
- •Handling customers complaints in a professional and diplomatic way.
- •Keeping the shop floor clean and tidy at all times.
- •Setting up promotional displays.

Transport manager Haulage Company- Bodan Sterling LTD 08.2015-present

Duties:

- •Responsible for getting the right products in the right quantities, to the right locations all at the right time.
- •In charge of the day to day operations of the transport department.
- •Efficiently managing a team of drivers and vehicles.
- •Responsible for all of the dispatching, routing, and tracking of delivery vehicles.
- •Dispatching complex and oversized goods to national and international destinations.
- •Ensuring company compliance of all transport policies, legislation and procedures to do with tachograph and towing etc.
- •Managing, monitoring and developing a team of drivers and line managers.
- •Involved in strategic development and strategy making.
- •Being the first point of contact for all drivers.
- •Making sure that all transport fleet vehicles are properly maintained and serviced.
- •Arranging for the induction and training off all new staff.
- •Regularly liaising with the delivery manager to ensure a smooth running of both departments.
- •Developing and nurturing customer relationships.
- •Maintaining accurate administrative records.
- •Giving drivers a full debrief, including tacho analysis.
- Organising vehicle checks.
- •Identifying operational issues, potential problems and opportunities.
- •Resolving and managing queries and complaints courteously and efficiently.
- •Appraising staff performance and also taking disciplinary measures when required.
- •Ensuring all site and customer objectives are achieved.

Skills:

- •A strong work ethic and desire to succeed.
- •Smart presentable appearance.
- •Possess a polite and helpful manner.
- •Confident communication skills.
- Willing to learn.
- Positive attitude.
- Confident and articulate.

Additional skills:

• Driving licence B category from 10.03.2015

- Proficient with Microsoft Suite Excel, Word, Internet and MS Windows
- Languages: Romanian(native speaking)

English(fluent)

French(entry level)

Spanish(entry level)

Academic qualifications:

- High School Graduation Diploma, graduate of "Carol I" Commerce High School, of Constanta city,Romania,technological studies in servicies,specialized as a Technician of commercial activities in 2014. Period of study: **2010-2014**
- Graduated of "I.C Bratianu" school on 2010
- Diploma in Journalism lvl 1 in Constanta city,Romania.- 2013

References: Avaible on request